All right, all
right, all right.
Let's play one
more time, okay?
And remember,
if I win,
you do not
move to Paris.
Okay. Can't believe
I'm risking this again,
but you're on.
All right, Joe,
you remember the rules--
heads I win, tails you lose.
Just flip.
Uh! Tails!
Damn it!
Hey!
So we thought we'd throw you
a little going-away party
around 7:00.
Oh, that sounds good.
Hey, Rache, you're
leaving tomorrow.
Shouldn't you be packing?
It's all done.
Oh, yeah, right.
And after I took a
shower this morning,
I just threw my
towel on the floor.
Oh, God, it hurts to
even joke about it.
I know.
Honey, seriously,
I did it all.
The luggage that I'm taking
is in the bedroom.
This is Emma's Paris stuff.
These are the boxes
that I'm having shipped,
and that's the sandwich
that I made for the plane.
Okay, so you've
done good work.
Yeah.
What about
your carry-ons?
Oh, well, everything
that I need is in here,
and my travel documents
are on the counter,
organized in the order
that I will be needing them.
Oh, my God.
I have nothing
left to teach you.
Oh...
Where's your
passport?
It should be
right next to my plane ticket.
Well, it-it's not.
What?
Well, maybe I put it in here?
Oh. Oh, it's not in there.
Oh, no. I must have packed it
in one of these boxes.
Here, let me help you.
Shoot.
RACHEL:
I can't believe
I did this.
Uh, at one point does
it stop being funny
that I took
the passport?
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ When the rain starts to pour ♪
♪ I'll be there for you ♪
♪ Like I've been there before ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Oh, wow, can you believe
you're only
three weeks away?
I know.
You don't
mind me touching
your belly, do you?
No, I don't mind you
touching my belly,
but right now your
hand's kind of
blocking the part where
the baby's gonna come out.
Hey.
Hi.
Hey, Erica, welcome
back to town.
Wow, look how big
you've gotten.
That's because I'm pregnant.
Right.
No, I-I understand.
Oh. Okay. I'm just always afraid
that people think
I'm just fat with big breasts.
No, no. I knew.
Great. Well,
stop staring at them.
Well, she brought them up.
I didn't realize
you were coming back so soon.
Yeah, well, in a
couple of weeks,
I won't be
able to travel.
Yeah, and I wanted her
to get to know the doctors
and get settled
into the hotel.
Hotel? Why isn't she
staying with you guys?
Well, because
we're moving
in a couple of days
and it just didn't make sense.
Plus, hotels are fun.
My room has this little fridge
full of free snacks.
Erica, those things aren't free.
In fact, they have
one of the highest markups
of any consumer product.
Ross,
she's giving us her baby.
She can eat you if she wants.
Be right back.
Oh, man, I can't believe you
guys are leaving this place.
I know, I know.
Hey, you know you could
take it if you want.
The lease is still
in Nana's name.
No, no, this will
always be your place.
It would be too sad.
Plus, how much a month
does it cost to feed Joey?
Yeah, it takes two incomes.
Yeah. Hey, is,
uh, Chandler here?
We talked about
catching a movie.
Oh, no, he doesn't
have time for that.
But if you want,
you can go help
him and Joey
pack up the guest room.
Hmm... packing...
sexy cheerleader comedy.
Hmm... helpful brother...
creepy loner at teen movie.
( gibbering )
What are you guys doing?
Try it. I can't feel a thing.
Are-are you kidding?
This is packing?
We're taking a break.
From...?
Jumping on the bed.
All right.
Rachel's party is in a couple of
hours, and there's a lot to do.
Now, Ross,
you've got Geller blood.
You're in charge
of these ya-hoos.
You got it.
All right.
All right, she's right,
we gotta get serious.
Let's put Styrofoam peanuts
down his pants and kick him.
No, no, no,
guys, she's right.
We should get to work.
I'll take stuff
out of the closet.
Joey, you pack them, and Ross,
you repack whatever Joey packs.
You guys hear a ringing?
What the hell is this?
Hey, handcuffs.
And fur-lined. Nice.
I didn't know you guys
had it in ya.
Chandler, you don't have a
sister, so you can't understand
how much this bums me out.
I didn't know
Monica had these.
Oh. Maybe she used them
with another boyfriend.
Maybe Richard. Yeah.
Why would she use them
with Richard and not me?
I can be kinky.
I once did a naked dance
for her... with scarves.
Bumming hard, guys.
Bumming hard.
( knock at door )
Hey.
Where's Mike?
Oh, he has a gig.
It's kind of like being married
to a rock star, you know.
"My husband has a gig."
Yeah? Where,
where is it?
Oh, he's playing organ
for a children's
roller-skating party.
Rock on.
Wow, this is
quite a spread.
What is
all this stuff?
Well, I thought
this would be
a great opportunity
to use up all the food
that I don't want to move
to the new house with me.
So... enjoy.
Smoked oyster casserole
with a breakfast
cereal crust.
Kidney beans in
their own juices,
and for dessert,
a questionable orange.
Hey.
Hey, where's Rache?
Oh, she's, uh, she's
putting Emma down.
She'll be over
in a second.
Now, it just hit her
that she's leaving
and she's kind of emotional,
so no one say anything
to set her off, okay?
Yeah.
ALL:
Hey.
Hey, Rach.
There she is.
( gasps )
Hi, you guys.
What did I just say?
Oh, no, no, no.
It's okay, it's okay.
I'm gonna be fine.
Come here, I'll
make you a drink.
Okay.
Oh, man, I can't believe
she's actually leaving.
How am I gonna say
good-bye to Rachel?
I know, she's been such
a big part of my life.
I mean, it feels like when
Melrose Place got canceled.
I mean...
Ah, forget it.
I miss Melrose Place.
Well, I had a chance
to stop her, too.
Yeah?
Who loses
57 coin tosses in a row?
You know?
Heads she wins, tails I lose.
Wait a minute.
Yes, Joe?
I forgot to pick up
my dry cleaning.
So, you doing okay?
Well, I've been better.
Mm-hmm.
You guys are gonna come
and visit me, right?
Yes. You know, in six months,
the statute of
limitations runs out
and I can travel
internationally again.
I'm gonna miss you so much.
I know.
You know what?
I have some good-bye stuff that
I wanted to say to each of you,
and I was gonna save it
till the end of the night,
but come here.
Come.
( door closes )
Hey, what do you think
they're doing in there?
Well, if I had to
guess, I'd say...
Rachel's putting on
the bubble wrap
and Phoebe's
doing the punching.
Oh, Phoebes, I don't
even know where to start.
Okay, well,
before you do...
Mm-hmm.
I know we weren't supposed
to get you going-away
presents, but...
I do have something for you.
Oh, Oh! Oh... What is it?
Well, it's a cotton swab
with a bit of my saliva on it.
So that... if they perfect
the cloning process
while you're over there,
you can use the DNA
to create your own Pheebs.
I'm gonna throw this away.
But thank you so
much for the gesture.
Chandler?
Um... I was just
in our bedroom
and I found these
on my pillow.
Oh, yes, I decided
to leave those out for you
in case Richard stops by
and you want to engage
in a little light bondage
and mustache play.
What are you
talking about?
These aren't mine.
Oh, yeah. Right.
Good luck getting
another scarf dance from me.
That would be a
terrible punishment.
But I'm serious. I've
never seen these before.
Really?
Then what are they doing
in our guest room?
Rachel used to
live in that room.
Rachel.
With handcuffs.
Interesting.
Joey's bare ass.
Well played.
I love you, Phoebe.
I love you, too.
Please.
Please don't...
don't turn into
you know, a French bitch.
All right.
Well, if I'm
gonna do this,
I'd better keep going.
Great.
Okay. Monica.
Yeah?
Will you come here
with me for a minute?
Sure.
Are you wearing
waterproof mascara?
No.
Oh, you're so screwed.
Hey.
What was that all about?
She's gonna say good-bye
to each of us individually.
Are you kidding?
Oh, my God.
Yeah, I know.
It's gonna be even
worse for you. God.
Well, just get ready to
do some serious crying.
Oh, man, I'm not going
to be able to handle this.
Now I know how my students
feel at the end of each year.
And why they act out by giving
me such bad evaluations.
Okay. I'd better...
just say what it is
I'm gonna say.
None of the amazing things
that have happened to me
in the last ten years
would have happened
if it wasn't for you.
No one has been...
more like a sister to me.
I know what you mean.
You're like a sister
to me, too.
( sniffling )
( choked up ):
I don't know what I'm
going to do without you.
( indecipherable )
What?
I... said... I...
( indecipherable )
That is so sweet.
Oh, no, she took down Monica.
And I'm the cryer in the family.
ROSS:
Oh, God,
I could be next.
Maybe she won't talk to me
if it looks like we're deep
in conversation.
Okay.
Oh, so that thing
you said about that thing,
it really made me think
about that other thing.
Uh, Rach...
Yeah?
It's okay.
Chandler's talking to her.
Really made you think
about that thing, huh?
Uh, Rach,
I think I have something
that belongs to you.
Oh, I'm sure going
to miss pretending
to laugh at your weird jokes
that I don't get.
No, no.
They're really yours.
We found them
in your old room.
Well, these aren't mine.
Maybe Monica used
to use them with...
Don't say Richard.
Well, if they're not Monica's
and they're not yours,
then whose are they?
I think
you're forgetting
the kinkiest
former resident
of that room.
Pheebs!
Yeah?
I think these are yours.
These are not mine.
Look at how flimsy they are.
Come on.
My God. You try to hang a guy
from a water pipe with these,
they'll snap
like a piece of licorice.
Can I talk to you
alone for a minute?
Sure.
You don't really
handcuff guys
to water pipes, do you?
Where do you think
Mike really is?
Oh, honey...
Let me just say something.
Because once we get
into this,
I'm going to get
all uncomfortable
and probably make
some stupid joke.
I just want to say
that I... I love you...
and I'm going
to miss you.
And I'm so sad
that you're leaving.
Oh, you know what?
Let's not say anything else.
I love you.
Not so tight.
( blows raspberry )
Oh!
Chandler...
I'm sorry.
Just give me
one more chance.
Okay.
Oh...
( blows raspberry )
Oh!
I'm sorry.
Just go. Just go.
I can't. I can't.
So I guess you're next.
You ready?
I don't think so.
Oh, you're
definitely not.
I haven't cried
like that in years.
You cried yesterday
at the 6:00 news.
That old woman was being scammed
by her mechanic.
God, I can't believe
she saved me for last.
Why are they taking so long?
I don't know,
but, God, Joey seems
to be handling it
surprisingly well.
ALL:
No! No, wait!
Okay, here we go.
( sighs )
Well.
Yeah.
I think I'm going
to take off.
Huh?
Oh, you guys, this was
an amazing night.
Thank you so much.
I love you.
Good night.
( door opens )
( door shuts )
What?!
I don't get a good-bye?!
Lucky bastard.
Unbelievable.
She says good-bye
to everyone but me.
Well, maybe she thought that
with all of your history,
it could be,
you know, implicit.
Well, it needs to be plicit!
Let's think about this.
I mean, there's got
to be an explanation.
Did you do anything
to make her mad?
No, I don't think so.
You know, maybe she was just
really spent from our talk.
It was pretty intense.
Yeah, mine, too.
Mine was a humdinger.
Okay!
I mean,
don't I deserve anything?
I mean, a... a few tears,
a... a cursory hug?
Not from you!
Ross, if you're this upset,
you should go and talk to her.
And say what?
"You owe me a good-bye"?
He's got more pride
than that.
The hell I do!
I don't get a good-bye?!
What?
Everyone gets
a good-bye but me?
What do I got to do
to get a good-bye, huh?
Uh, be best friends with you?
Uh, go out with you?
Have-have a baby with you?
Oh, wait a minute!
Wait a minute!
I did all those things!
Ross, I...
Or maybe...
Maybe I'm just
not giving you
enough credit.
Uh, I mean, it is difficult
to say good-bye to fivepeople.
Uh, "Good-bye. Good-bye,
Good-bye. Good-bye.
( choking up ):
Goo..."
It's physically impossible!
You know what, after all we've
been through, I can't believe
this is how you want
to leave things between us.
Have a... have a good time
in Paris.
I hope Ross
isn't too upset.
I'm sure he's not
more bummed out
than I am.
Tell me about it.
Well, you can't say
we don't know how
to throw a party.
All right, I think
I'm going to head out.
Uh, where do you think
you're going?
I thought I was going home
to go to bed, but I'm sensing
there's something less fun
for me to do here.
Well, we're moving
in a couple of days,
and we got a lot
of packing to do.
It'd be great if you guys
could pitch in.
Joey and I can finish up
in the guest room.
Oh, yeah, yeah. Good idea.
Oh, no.
You and Phoebe are going
to help me in here.
You couldn't be cool.
Okay, we're going to
start in the kitchen.
Plates get put
into plate protectors
and get stacked ten to a box.
The silverware gets bundled
in rubber bands
and then bubble-wrapped.
Got it?
Yeah.
Good.
Now I need you
to be careful
and efficient.
And remember,
if I am harsh with you,
it's only because
you're doing it wrong.
Hey, Mon, I think I figured out
whose handcuffs they are.
You did? How?
Well, I was cleaning
out the closet
and I found some pictures
of them... being used.
Oh, my God.
Let me see.
( gasps )
Who's that dirty old lady?
Monica's grandmother.
God, Nana liked it rough!
Hi.
Hey.
Here, have a seat.
Have a seat.
How was your night?
Oh, it was okay.
I went to a movie
with my cousin
and then out for dinner.
We went to this place
that had...
Ooh!
Ooh.
( sighs )
Anyway, they had these really
amazing cheeseburgers.
Erica, are you okay?
Yeah. You know,
maybe I ate too much.
I keep getting
these stomachaches.
The come and go like
every few minutes.
Oh, my God!
Relax, we'll just get her
some antacids.
She doesn't have a stomachache!
She's in labor!
On, my God!
Yeah, you got to get
to the hospital!
Okay, Chandler,
get the coats!
Erica, let's go!
Phoebe and Joey,
keep packing!
Oh, my God, we're going...
We're going
to have a baby!
Oh, my God!
We're going to have a baby!
Oh, God, I've got to sit down!
I got to sit down. Oh!
( labored breathing )
Honey, it's going
to be okay.
You can do this! Just breathe.
Okay, okay.
Okay, I feel...
I feel a little better.
Oh!
Are you sure?
Oh, yes, I'm sure.
Oh, honey, let's go.
Okay.
Come on.
Okay, bye,
everyone!
Bye-bye. We're having a baby!
Chandler, wait, wait, wait!
What?
If you get a second,
find out where
she got that cheeseburger.
( door slams )
You really think
I didn't say good-bye to you
because I don't care?
That's what it seemed like.
I cannot believe
that after ten years,
you do not know
one thing about me.
Fine. Then why didn't you
say something?
Because it is too damn hard,
Ross.
I can't even begin
to explain to you
how much I am going
to miss you.
When I think about
not seeing you
every day, it makes
me not want to go,
okay?
So if you think
that, that
I didn't say good-bye to you
because you don't mean as much
to me as everybody else,
you're wrong.
It's because
you mean more to me.
So there, all right?!
There's your good-bye!
Rach.
What?
You ca... you can't...
What?!
A little more.
Okay.
All right.
A little more.
Okay.
All right. Okay.
All right,
let's do this.
All right, ready?
Yep. Now give me
your best shot.
All right, here goes.
( strained voice ):
Doesn't work.
Oh!
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org